uh... that was the verdict i hope that
there's going to be ensured zero i don't
think so
uh... because only four of showing call
it a few things working today
which is very
pretty awesome sold it so that you are
recovered a bit
or assisted up w conceiving
want targeted it automatically jumps
teresa d_p_s_
that it is just a search engine for
details on their feet on the role of the
parole
stocks which have become the interesting
so for example if they want to search
for something for example for
template uh... uh...
it already gives me
uh... some suggestions here and i can
pick one of them
and uh... if you need me to jumps to one
of the solutions
of their recommended
and what was what you can see here is
the documentation of the mortal but the
point where interesting at this
that the taiko says that actually you
can possible at each ward or simply
click handed a specification concept
that already two people have at cost it
uh... so
uprooted from whatever that means
and uh... it's not because it sort of
part of a biblical and ordered to people
here
so how can i think click on that swamped
if i click on it and some dot that i
have to sign up so how do i do that
he reckons
that occupying upbeat and they'll be the
counsel people who don't have the pose
account
sign up for you
yahoo co gi publicly for and probably by
the time your watching that this is a
little you together and approach they
are still at uh... driving spose because
i am adult for here
and that's not a cure
they might handle at photos
and i wanted aidid this it's up to the
defense meat and email to my pose
account to verify that it indeed me
so they go to the state-owned and a
and give it my gmail account and here i
think that there is a link am
there are so computed the smallest here
just to learn teaching depleting the
taps
and what i did this
historically
coordinator for mario
uh... autos didn't follow it if you
don't have an open certify that all the
fields are going to be empty and then
you can feel out all the because i think
you name and adopting a whatever dot and
you want to show up in the new email and
all of you
that'd be against it or decide to my my
picture marta avatar
uh...
from the graft or reply
and uh... then you can ensure that the
country
so you can contact it to your accountant
you can actually check better you talk
to type came uh... actually maps to
rightfully
what i call to character s
and i can come here or and also connect
superiors
yeah i don't think you know i ordered
there have been
inhaled and already connected to each
one of the day accounts argues nichols
was collected by their find out
but i haven't been around edu
it'd be that counts
life i come back here
uh... through the template and every
little disparage
and then he tells me that i did
could actually possible to climb up
icons anymore because i already did it
during their sleep a click here
then it will be moved across all that i
thought that they can
so i at that point and then i can search
for something else
and and
that's me
recognizes
and then i can find here all these
modules and for example there is a w_ w_
mechanized her life can be used to quite
a lot so i want to ask plus want there
to do
and yourself
but didn't have a cross on the elections
one
so i hope that you can come by and uh...
join us that telling which would to his
which would which would be id used in
them
which would be neglected
thank you for watching that and uh...
probably because without their accounts
again in their mind outpost let me my
and uh...
metaphysical
thank you very much